# Show-UI is the merger of two projects: WPK and PowerBoots.
# At various times, both projects have had user feedback either 
# because they too long to load, or because they did not load completely
# Show-UI fixes this by switching the backbone of the project 
# (a code generator that lets you create cmdlets for WPF controls)
# from a script generator to a C# generator.

# This has several advantages:

# - Load time drops thru the floor
# - The memory footprint drops considerably
# - Because the generated code is built once, the distributable will be a lot smaller

# Let's go ahead and do a clean generation of the module.  

# Please make sure you have not loaded the any process, it will not be able to clean.
# This will take a while, and we'll use Measure-Command to know just how long
Measure-Command { 
    Import-Module 'Show-UI' -ArgumentList 'Clean' -Force
}

# Ok, now let's import this the second time, the way most users should.
Measure-Command { 
    Import-Module 'Show-UI' -Force
}


